perfectseotools.com 2012-06-22

# Privacy Policy | Perfect SEO Tools

####  Overview

Perfect SEO Tools believes that strong electronic privacy is crucial for the ongoing success of the Internet as a service, commercial and entertainment medium. To this end, unless you designate otherwise, the information you enter here will be known to only two parties: you and Perfect SEO Tools. We pledge that Perfect SEO Tools will not release your personal data to anyone else without your consent - period. You may change the status of whether you wish to receive Perfect SEO Tools offers and communications at any time. When we do present information to our advertisers, unless you tell us otherwise, it is in the form of aggregate statistics compiled among all of our visitors' answers to survey questions as well as grouped on-site behavior. We do our best to provide as much security as possible concerning personal information and registration data.

####  What information does Perfect SEO Tools gather/track?

Each time a visitor comes to a Perfect SEO Tools Web site, we collect following kinds of personal data to improve the overall quality of the online experience.   
(a) information about your computer and about your visits to use Perfect SEO Tools, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referralsource, length of visit and number of page views.  
(b) information relating to any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our services (including your name, email address, place of employmentand credit card details)  
(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of registering with us (including your name, email address and otherpersonal information supplied by you) 

####  Your access to your information

You have a right to request a copy of any personal information that we hold about you. You will be asked for appropriate identification when you request copies of personal information. If you register with this website, your account will include a personal storage area called Profile Area. You can access and change your stored information at any time by logging in. Provision of such information may be subject to the payment of a fee (currently fixed at £10).

####  Cookies

Perfect SEO Tools, employs "cookies" to provide users with tailored information. A "cookie" is an element of data that a website, when visited by a user, sends to that user's browser which, in turn, may store that element on the user's hard drive or memory. Perfect SEO Tools, uses cookies to better serve users of this website; any cookies sent by Perfect SEO Tools, will be marked so that they will be accessible only by Perfect SEO Tools site, subject to this Privacy Statement.  
We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: [ http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html).  
Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in InternetExplorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”,“Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites (including this one).

####  International data storage locations

Information that we collect maybe stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

If you are in the European Union, information which you provide may be transferred to countries (including the United States) which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Union. You expressly agree to such transfers.

####  Links with other websites

The Perfect SEO Tools site contain links to other websites, whether owned or controlled by Perfect SEO Tools, affiliates, or unrelated third parties. Please note that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from those of the Perfect SEO Tool site. Perfect SEO Tools, is not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of any linked website. We encourage you to read the privacy statement of any website you may visit.

####  Third Party Advertising

We use several third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

####  No Guarantees for factors beyond Perfect SEO Tools’ Control

While this Privacy Statement expresses Perfect SEO Tools, standards for maintenance of private data, it is not in a position to guarantee that the standards will always be met.

####  Security

To secure site integrity, Perfect SEO Tools, employs security measures and procedures. Internal access to users' private and nonpublic personal information is restricted to site administrators.

####  Enforcement

In the event that Perfect SEO Tools, becomes aware that site security is compromised or nonpublic user information has been disclosed to unrelated third parties as a result of external activity, Perfect SEO Tools, shall take reasonable measures which it deems appropriate, including investigation and reporting, and notification to and cooperation with law enforcement authorities, notwithstanding other provisions of this Privacy Statement.

####  Policy Amendments

From time to time, Perfect SEO Tools may introduce new products and services to its users. To the extent these new products and services affect this policy, this policy will be updated. To update the Privacy Statement, we will post both the changed version and its effective date at [ http://www.perfectseotools.com/information/privacy-policy.aspx](http://www.perfectseotools.com/information/privacy-policy.aspx)

####  Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to
